Listen up. This is very important and
you need to watch this till the end. So,
Trump just signed a directive to
accelerate 6G deployment, which will
help operate implantable technologies,
which includes AI brain chips, known as
biological interface system to cortex.
It was announced in December of 2025. It
is a paper-thin flexible silicone chip,
[music]
and it looks like that.
There's already research on security
issues with this kind of tech. The five
paramount security and privacy issues
are authentication, access control,
malicious behavior, encryption, and
communication. Not only that, but
there's studies of the risk to health
and well-being from radio frequency
radiation emitted by cell phones and
other wireless devices. Because even
when you get a new phone, it has a paper
in there that you're supposed to read,
and it tells you that you're not
supposed to hold your phone to your face
because it is dangerous. And it's
already dangerous with 5G, so just
imagine when it's 6G. December the 22nd,
the White House orders federal agencies
to free lower 7 GHz band for commercial
6G. Do you all remember when the
sickness was going around, and at the
same time these towers were going up,
and then a lot of people were getting
sick? And if you look up the symptoms
for radiation poisoning, it looked a lot
like the symptoms that were appearing.
Oh, and did I mention that they're
wanting to do this without any studies
being done of the safety risk? On top of
that, Trump is now slamming banks over
crypto bill hold up, urges Congress to
pass act [music] ASAP. Because one day,
and it looks like very soon in the
future, everyone is going to get a mark,
and that mark is going to be connected
to your money, and it will be used to
control whether you can buy or sell.
Now, if we look at this patent right
here, it's 060606.
It's the cryptocurrency system using
body activity data. Human body activity
associated with the task provided to a
user may be used in a mining process of
a cryptocurrency system. A server may
provide a task to a device of a user
which is communicatively coupled to the
server. This sensor that people will
have in them may sense body activity of
the user. The net body activity data may
be generated based on the sensed body
activity of the user. Then it will
verify if your body activity data
satisfies one or more conditions set by
the cryptocurrency system and award
cryptocurrency or pay you if your body
activity data is verified. As in if you
do what they tell you to you will get
paid your cryptocurrency. So they're
about to install this system
that can run these things. Scientists
want to use people as antennas to power
6G. So we will be the ones powering 6G.
We're going to be used as antennas. And
just like this patent says, the chips
that are going to be implanted in people
will be connected to this system. You
will be used as an antenna and they will
be able to sense your body activity and
reward you your money if you do what
they tell you to do. And that is why he
is urging Congress to pass this act
because in order to control you you have
to get rid of actual money and everybody
has to have a stablecoin wallet which is
exactly what this man is doing. We have
been warning everyone about this for
years. The beast system is being built
right in front of you. If you do not
have a relationship with Jesus, you need
to get one immediately. The Bible says
that if you confess with your mouth that
Jesus is Lord and believe that he died,
was buried, and rose again for the
remission of your sins you will be
saved. Don't wait until it's too late.